Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
- (So far) Unsorted Leftovers
  - Non-Audio Unsorted Stuff
    - AllSongs, Notes: Whiteish box with the title on spine. The front says "ALLSONGS Files Complete Listings" with clipart of trees, bats and a spider. Origin: Paula's Big Box of Filk; File Box 1 copy (Box Box #(Q))
      Various; Paula's Big Box of Filk; File Box
    - Filk & Folk, Notes: Dappled beige binder with art of a guitarist and another guy in classic rock poses. The front says "FILK & FOLK - Songs of Fandom Courtesy of John Hall, DI" Origin: Paula's Big Box of Filk - Collection of John Hall; Binder 1 copy (Box Box #(Q))
      Various; Paula's Big Box of Filk - Collection of John Hall; Binder
    - Caught on the Web, Notes: Dappled blue binder with art of s spider on a web. Origin: Paula's Big Box of Filk; Binder 1 copy (Box Box #(Q))
      Various; Paula's Big Box of Filk; Binder
    - Silver binder, Notes: Silver binder, unlabeled spine Origin: Paula's Big Box of Filk; Binder 1 copy (Box Box #(Q))
    - SWIL Filkbook, Notes: Dark green binder with Swil Filkbook on the spin, witha picture of a castle-like building Origin: Paula's Big Box of Filk; Binder 1 copy (Box Box #(Q))
    - Babylon 5 Our Last, Best Hope ..., Notes: White binder with Babylon 5 logo and title on a stip of blue paper Origin: Paula's Big Box of Filk; Binder 1 copy (Box Box #(Q))
    - Phydeaux Philque, Notes: White binder with a pink strip of paper with the title in a weird 1990s font. Origin: Paula's Big Box of Filk; Binder 1 copy (Box Box #(Q))
    - Leslie, Tom and Joe, Notes: Black binder with reddish strip of paper with the title. Origin: Paula's Big Box of Filk; Binder 1 copy (Box Box #(Q))
      Fish, Leslie, Smith, Tom, Bethancourt, Joe; Paula's Big Box of Filk; Binder
    - Jewel case & liner notes for "It's Sister Jenny's Turn to Throw the Bomb", Notes: no actual tape Origin:; Liner notes 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
      Liner notes
    - Liner notes for "Dragonsongs", Notes: no tape or case Origin:; Liner notes 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
    - Empty shipping envelope with Gary McGath's address, Notes: Origin:; 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
    - OVFF 2014 progress report postmarked 06 Sep 2014, Notes: addressed at 363 Hauser Ave, forwarded to 32 Demott Pl Origin:; Progress report 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
      Progress report
    - The Filk Foundation Directory of Members, Jan 1985, Notes: Origin:; List of filkers 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
      List of filkers
    - The Filk Foundation Directory of Members & Former Members / July 1981, Notes: Origin:; List of filkers 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
    - Tomorrow's Songs Today, Notes: Origin:; 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
      Gary McGath
    - Harpings #3 (with OVFF 2 materials attached), Notes: Origin:; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
      Margaret Middleton; Zine
    - Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non Number Thirteen-A September 25, 1982, Notes: Origin:; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
    - 2017 Worldcon Site Selection Ballot instructions, Notes: Origin:; 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
    - Computer Blues, Notes: Origin:; Song lyrics 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
      Stan Rogers; Song lyrics
    - Harpings #9 (with Directory of Members Feb 1987 & List of Publications & Recordings), Notes: Origin:; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
    - Harpings #2, Notes: Origin:; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
    - Harpings #4, Notes: Origin:; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
    - Harpings #12, Notes: Origin:; Zine 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
    - Filk Songs (Beginning 1994) 2014 Edition, Notes: Origin:; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
      Ed Chamberlain; Songbook
    - From The Cockpit, Notes: Presented By Con-Chord and the Philk Fee-Nom-Ee-Non Origin:; Songbook 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
    - Con-Chord Filk-Con 5.1 March 11-13, 1983 Program Book, Notes: Origin:; Program book 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
      Program book
    - Program and Cribsheets for Bayfilk One, Notes: Origin:; Program book 1 copy (Box Box #29 (MM))
    - Locus, January 2012, Notes: Origin:; Magazine copy (Box JW #22)
    - Town & Country Resort Property Map, Notes: Town & Country in San Diego is a common venue for many cons Origin:; Map 2 copy (Box JW #22)
      Map
    - Kazoo Award Ballot, 2015, Notes: Origin:; Ballot copy (Box JW #22)
    - HeroClix foldable playing board, Notes: received as a demo, probably at a LosCon Origin:; Game copy (Box JW #22)
      Game
    - San Diego Fandom Index Oct. 2013 Issue #20, Notes: Origin:; 2 copy (Box JW #22)
    - Envelope with Jesse Weinstein's name and city, previously containing badges from NADWCon 2013, Notes: now contains "What does Terry Pratchett mean to you?" ad, Discworld Emporium ad, & pog from Ronald Soak Origin:; copy (Box JW #22)
    - Westercon 68 Progress Report 3, Notes: Origin:; Progress report copy (Box JW #22)
    - David Gerrold Worldcon 2015 Sampler, Notes: Origin:; copy (Box JW #22)
      David Gerrold
    - Pulp Literature Isssue # 8, Notes: Origin:; copy (Box JW #22)
    - Hitchkier's Guide to Loscon 42, Notes: Origin:; Program booklet copy (Box JW #22)
      Program booklet
    - Loscon 42 Pocket Program, Notes: even though it's titled "Pocket Program" it's actually a schedule grid, but in large font Origin:; Schedule grid 2 copy (Box JW #22)
      Schedule grid
    - Amok Time Outdoor Trek, Notes: Origin:; Program copy (Box JW #22)
      Program
    - Confilkt 9, Notes: title not on cover Origin:; Program booklet 2 copy (Box JW #22)
    - Bag of badges, Notes: from a variety of cons, with ribbons Origin:; copy (Box JW #22)
    - Rise Up Singing (15th Anniversary Edition), Notes: Origin:; Commercial Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
    - Along Fantasy Way, Notes: published by Lee Gold Origin:; Zine 2 copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Digby, Tom; Zine
    - Dr. Jane's Songs, Notes: Origin:; Songbook 2 copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Robinson, Dr. James; Songbook
    - Echo's Children -- Songbook 2003, Notes: Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Echo's Children; Songbook
    - Songworm: Segment 3, Notes: Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Kanefsky, Bob; Songbook
    - The Filkaholic Strikes Again..., Notes: Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Brener, Mara & Brener, Harry & Brener, Maddy; Songbook
    - [Untitled collection of photocopied folk songs; cover page is "Across the great divide"], Notes: Origin:; Song lyrics copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Song lyrics
    - Filker Up #1, Notes: Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Gold, Lee; Songbook
    - Filker Up #2, Notes: Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
    - Filker Up #3, Notes: Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
    - Filker Up #4, Notes: Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
    - Filker Up #5, Notes: Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
    - Filker Up #6, Notes: Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
    - Images of Wilbur Whately from a panel (probably Loscon, unclear what year), Notes: Origin:; Handout copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Handout
    - High Fly the Nazgul, Notes: Origin:; Song lyrics copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Ted Johnstone; Song lyrics
    - Windigo's Coming, Notes: Origin:; Song lyrics copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Eileen McGann; Song lyrics
    - Filking at LASFS (June 26, 2008), Notes: 14 pages of various classic filk songs Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Lee Gold; Songbook
    - Atheists United Songbook (Last Updated Dec 23, 2008), Notes: 50 pages, unbound Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
    - Walker Community United Methodist Church Songbook, Notes: 190 pages, index taped onto the back, missing cover; spiral bound Origin:; Songbook copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
    - The X Filks / Ten years of FilkCONtinental, Notes: Origin:; Songbook|Program Book copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)
      Songbook|Program Book
    - Various misc photocopies of folk songs, Notes: Origin:; Songsheet copy (Box JW Blue suitcase)